## Geidel Guerra

#### Software Developer

https://geidelguerra.com

### **Summary**

Self-taught Software Developer with several years of work. Enjoys the challenges that each project presents. Loves Javascript, VueJs and NodeJs ecosystem. Scholar of Stoicism. Casual Gamer. Avid reader with the right book. Honest and straightforward.

### Skills

- VueJs
- Laravel
- Javascript
- CSS
- HTML
- PHP
- Nuxt
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- Git
- Basic RESTful APIs

### Other skills

• Unity3D

## Skills to develop

- NodeJs
- ReactJs
- Electron
- NoSQL database

### Languages

- Spanish (native)
- English (good at reading, listening and writing, can improve at speaking)

### **Experience**

# Fullstack Developer at Artcrónica (Cuban Visual Arts Magazine) July 2018 – Present

# Fullstack Developer at Fábrica de Arte Cubano (Multi-cultural center in Havana)

December 2014 – June 2018 (3 years and 6 months)

# Videogame Developer at Joven Club de Computación y Electrónica October 2013 – December 2014 (1 year and 3 months)

### **Education**

### Universidad Tecnológica de La Habana José Antonio Echeverría

Engineering, Information Technology 2006 – 2009 (didn't graduate)

#### Mártires de Chile

High School, Information Technology 2002 – 2006

### Showcase

### Alberto Hernández Reyes Personal Website (July 2018 – Present)

https://albertohreyes.com

Nuxt + Tailwindcss + Netlify

### La Tinta Magazine Website (March 2018 – Present)

https://latintamagazine.com

Nuxt + Tailwindcss + Netlify

### Artcrónica Website (July 2018 – Present)

https://www.artcronica.com

#### Wordpress

**Gráfica Interactiva 3 (Art presentation collaboration) (October 2017)** Unity3D 5

Gráfica Interactiva 2 – Eyeife Special (Art presentation collaboration) (September 2017)

Unity3D 5

Gráfica Interactiva 2 – Eyeife Special (Art presentation collaboration) (September 2017)

Unity3D 5

**Gráfica Interactiva 2 (Art presentation collaboration) (March 2017)** Unity3D 5

**Gráfica Interactiva 2 (Art presentation collaboration) (March 2017)**Unity3D 5

**Gráfica Interactiva 1 (Art presentation collaboration) (June 2015)**Unity3D 5

Fábrica de Arte Cubano Website (January 2015 – June 2018) Laravel 5, MySQL